All right, guys, let's move to the second play, employee image.
Now imagine that same doctor walking into the room
looking like he just rolled out of bed.
How would you react?
You'd definitely have some questions. But why?
That is because appearance creates confidence.
Before you say one word, your image tells a story.
At Team WOW, a clean, complete uniform says, "I'm
ready, I'm professional, and I am proud to represent my
team."
That means the correct uniform, proper hat or visor, good
personal hygiene, and meeting our image standards from the moment you
clock in.
Now, Coach isn't about to ask you to look like you just walked into the Met Gala,
but you've got to look game ready.
Let's look and see what penalties we can find in this
one.
All right, guys, let's move to the second play, employee
image. Now imagine that same doctor
walking into the room looking like he just rolled out of
bed. How would you react? You'd definitely have some
questions. But why? That is
because appearance creates confidence.
Before you say one word, your image tells a story.